<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rishidesai</title>
    <link>therishidesai.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on rishidesai</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="therishidesai.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>therishidesai.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>therishidesai.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Currently I am a Software Engineer at Anduril Industries. I studied Computer Science at the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign. Most of my programming interests are in building systems software (Operating Systems, Compilers, etc.) to enable Robotics, AR/VR, and other spatial compute.
In addition to programming, I am a huge Bay Area sports fan, which I consistently tweet about. I also enjoy spending time outdoors on my bike or skateboard, and playing basketball and soccer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organizations</title>
      <link>therishidesai.github.io/organizations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>therishidesai.github.io/organizations/</guid>
      <description>Organizations   ACM@UIUC I was a member of the Illinois ACM student chapter for 4 years. During that time I serverd as the Vice Chair of ACM during the 2018-2019 school year and for 2 years I was the lead of ACM projects where we worked on many of the projects here.
  HackIllinois I helped plan HackIllinois 2018 and 2019; specifically focused on the hacker and mentor experience during the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>therishidesai.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>therishidesai.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Open Source Projects:   ACM GPU Cluster Built the docker container management system for the GPU cluster that allows users to have GPU access from a jupyter notebook running in a docker container. This project uses the nvdocker python library we made to create and run docker containers with GPU access. Essentially we built Google CoLab before Google did.
  nvdocker nvdocker is library built on top of the docker-py python sdk to build and run docker containers with GPU access using nvidia-docker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>therishidesai.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>therishidesai.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>ILLIXR Worked with Professor Sarita Adve&amp;rsquo;s group for 2 years on the ILLIXR Extended Reality benchmark and runtime. This benchmark enables full system profiling and prototyping for systems and architecture researchers working in AR/VR/XR. I helped with the early design of the runtime and contributed to building out the build and dependency management system. I also worked on porting OpenVINS, a Visual Inertial Odometry system, to our runtime. In addition, I profiled OpenVINS using the runtime and other tools (linux perf and Intel VTune) for architecture insights that coud be used for a custom SLAM/VIO accelerator.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>